const flashcardsContent = [
  { question: "Chlorate", answer: "ClO₃⁻" },
  { question: "Chlorite", answer: "ClO₂⁻" },
  { question: "Perchlorate", answer: "ClO₄⁻" },
  { question: "Hypochlorite", answer: "ClO⁻" },
  { question: "Nitrite", answer: "NO₂⁻" },
  { question: "Nitrate", answer: "NO₃⁻" },
  { question: "Sulfate", answer: "SO₄²⁻" },
  { question: "Sulfite", answer: "SO₃²⁻" },
  { question: "Hydrogen Sulfate", answer: "HSO₄⁻" },
  { question: "Hydrogen Sulfite", answer: "HSO₃⁻" },
  { question: "Phosphate", answer: "PO₄³⁻" },
  { question: "Hydrogen Phosphate", answer: "HPO₄²⁻" },
  { question: "Dihydrogen Phosphate", answer: "H₂PO₄⁻" },
  { question: "Carbonate", answer: "CO₃²⁻" },
  { question: "Bicarbonate", answer: "HCO₃⁻" },
  { question: "Permanganate", answer: "MnO₄⁻" },
  { question: "Chromate", answer: "CrO₄²⁻" },
  { question: "Dichromate", answer: "Cr₂O₇²⁻" },
  { question: "Ammonium", answer: "NH₄⁺" },
  { question: "Hydronium", answer: "H₃O⁺" },
  { question: "Acetate", answer: "CH₃CO²⁻" },
  { question: "Cyanide", answer: "CN⁻" },
  { question: "Azide", answer: "N₃⁻" },
  { question: "Peroxide", answer: "O₂²⁻" },
  { question: "Hydroxide", answer: "OH⁻" },
];

export default flashcardsContent;